

Kurdistan Salih Majeed

MRF Quatro Towers , Erbil , Iraq 07728880088 Kurdasalah92@gmail.com

> Gender : Female Nationality : Iraqi

EDUCATION

July 2015 Diploma in Management and Accounting

British Institute for Accounting and Management (BIAM)

June 2013 High School Diploma

American Classical School of the Medes

Oct 2018 Certificate of Project Management Professional Training

Qandil Organization

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Professional

- Experienced in dealing with people, diffusing tense situation and reaching accord.
- Comfortable with harsh working environments
- Skilled with computers and communication equipment
- Good typing speed
- Experience of working at Humanitarian Organization
- Interpreting skills

Personal Summary

Keen and dedicated aid worker with experience in various fields. Strong believer in ethical work and providing aid where needed. Have experience of humanitarian aid. Have worked with homeless individuals and refugees suffering from the effects of war and immigration. Capable at managing high pressure situations and negotiating peaceful outcomes despite cultural barriers .Excellent language skills and good grasp of technology , hands-on help to people in need.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Admin and HR
- Data Entry
- Communication
- Protection
- Procurement

Languages	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Kurdish	Mother tongue	Mother tongue	Mother tongue
English	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent
Arabic	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent

EXPERIENCE

May 2019 – Sept 2019 KINTEC GLOBAL – Admin Officer

- Manage daily HR & Admin , finance, logistic tasks of the office
- General administration duties supporting Operations Manager with preparation of general correspondence.
- Preparing business letters and reports
- Arrange hotel accommodation and travels
- Coordination of company's postal service and couriers
- Monitor and track rotation of Contractors/Operation Manager
- Setup office filing system
- Taxation payments submitted to ministry
- Legislation and apostle documents
- Answering phone calls

- Collect and analyse necessary information and data for tracking progress
- Answering phone calls in a mannerly way from refugees and reporting to M&E manager
- Closely accompany Qandil's activities subject to priority
- Attending meetings and trainings held by Qandil
- Assisting procurement manager and preparing purchase request and processing data

- Ensure that the correct policies and procedures are followed during the time of implementation
- Visiting fields and following up the needs of the refugees
- Responsible for preparing meeting room, audio visual equipment, name tags
- Other duties including administrational

Sept 2016- July 2017 **NEWROZ TELECOM** – International connection admin

- Interface with customer finance and technical
- Reporting monthly to Sales Manager
- Responsible to meet the customers and suppliers of the sales department
- Preparing contracts
- Attend meetings with international suppliers
- Attend trainings about telecom skills held by Newroz Telecom
- Visiting the telecom fields and reporting to supervisor
- Maintain the company's wholesale filing system of the suppliers and customers
- Prepare administrative documents

Feb 2016- Aug 2016 KURDISTAN SAVE THE CHILDREN ORGANIZATION {KSC} - Volunteer

- Monitoring
- Collect data while visiting the children
- Arrange festivals and science and musical fares for the children
- Supporting the M&E manager with daily report on each child's case and needs
- Providing aids for Hiwa Hospital children with cancer

	Name	Email Address	Contact	Posistion
-	Mustafa Kemal	Mustafa.kemal@newroztelecom.com	07501689185	Wholesale Supervisor - Newroz Telecom

- Araz Barwari <u>Araz.barwari@qandil.se</u>

07504046404 Legal Advisor-Qandil Organization